[{"answer": "Well, I -- you know somebody might argue with you on that, but I'd have trouble finding anyone better.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Would it be too far, Mr. Welch, to go out and say he was the greatest CEO of our time, maybe ever?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "That is the big question.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "So the question is, how is this going to affect Apple products down the road?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I think he's just -- you know, he was a marketing genius.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "In a word or two, what would you think his legacy is going to be?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I really wrote that piece because when Steve Jobs got sick there was a lot of discussion about how great a leader he was.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "How great of a leader, Steve, was he?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, you know, F. Scott Fitzgerald said there are no second acts in American lives and Steve Jobs proved Fitzgerald wrong.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "How did he do that?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "He was -- you know what, he was always interested in every technical, electronic gadget there was in the world.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What was he like in those days?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Steve Jobs, definitely.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Who would have been more successful if you hadn't met each other?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I am still an Apple employee.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "You're still an Apple employee, aren't you?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "I think the check -- I don't even see it, but I think it's a couple hundred bucks every two weeks.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "How much do you get?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "My wife and I really aren't big stock traders.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Do you have a stake in the company at all these days?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Giving mankind the most useful, helpful tools we've ever had in our history, the ones we would enjoy the most, the ones that we not only use but we love, that we come to love, like a human being.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "In terms of what you know of him, what do you think he'd like the legacy to be, the Steve Jobs legacy to be?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "It's hard to say.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Was the computer, in which you were very instrumental in producing -- is that going to be the greatest invention of, you know, the last millennium?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I don't think we could stop the effect of the future, the future we created giving them devices.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "And they should be out playing Conquers (ph) and soccer and stuff like that, shouldn't they?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "You know, we were so prepared for this.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What goes through your mind on this sad day?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Steve was very focused.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Or was he simply focused on technology?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I met him, but I really never had a chance to actually interview him.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Did you get to know him a little bit?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Well, there's been a lot of speculation about that for a long time, Wolf.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "What is going to happen to Apple, Andy, now that Steve Jobs unfortunately has passed away?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "And I think you're in this business now because of him, is that right?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "Wolf, it's also a busy place here as people who admired Steve Jobs are stopping by, leaving flowers and a few hand made signs as well.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What's happening over there, Susan?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "I got a Tweet from my friend.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "How did you hear about the death?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "It was just simplicity overall.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "What attracted you -- that won't change, I should say -- but what attracted you to Steve Jobs and to the Apple products?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: At 14.", "docId": "111005pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "You bought your first Apple product at what age?", "qSentId": 701}]